It's over. He wants to break up with me.
- His mother cried after we had the meeting.
You showed me off and looked down on Jung Hoon.
You hurt his mom's pride.
Mom, you must be happy that it turned out the way you wanted.
I don't care if you're going to set me blind dates or not.
Just leave me alone right now.
I asked you why you aren't saying anything.
Why are you acting like this? What's wrong?
- We broke up.
- You broke up with Hye Yoon?
I like you, noonim.
You shouldn't have touched my wife.
- Oppa.
- Don't cry. I'm a player.
Trash.
My fahter is done reviewing our marriage.
My family is done reviewing as well.
- When should we meet each other's parents?
- Let's do it next week.
Let's move quickly if we have decided.
It's been a long time.
Are you crazy?
Hye Yoon just came and went. Weren't you two supposed to meet up?
She was a little weird. She is different from normal. She has her mind elsewhere. She almost got hit by my bike!
And she was talking about a weird poem and habits or something.
Episode 4 : Defend a wedding hall
I hope you were flustered because I asked to meet with you.
No, I wanted to meet you too.
Just like we said, i set the date.
While I was finding the date, I found out their marital compatibility is very good.
- But the kids~
- - In-law.
They fight while preparing their wedding.
We must help them get back together.
But we can't force them to be together.
That's right, but in this situation no matter who looks at it, they didn't break up because they lost affection.
You think it is because of me?
No, how could it be because of you?
- It's because of me.
- No...
- I'm sorry.
- No, Hye Yoon's mother.
I was very emotional that day.
Jung Hoon is an amazing man.
Thank you for raising him well and giving him to Hye Yoon.
I feel ashamed if you come out like this.
In-law, i wish to get along.
I wish that too. But it depends on Jung Hoon.
The only reason why I accepted this marriage
was because my son wanted Hye Yoon.
But now that has become unclear so I don't know what to do.
Should i broke off this engagement?
But my heart hurts to hear that Hye Yoon's heart hurts.
I'll at least try talking to Jung Hoon.
- Where are you going?
- It's stuffy.
Don't do this marriage.
Even if you tell me to do it, I won't be able to. Don't worry.
I met Jung Hoon's mom. She's so insecure.
Why you met her? She was upset at you because of the meeting.
So I met her to resolve it.
Resolve what? You probably set it on fire.
Mom, you don't want for me to be happy, do you?
I devoted my life for the happiness of you and your sister.
What are you talking about?
You always say that. Do you know how hard it was for me and my sister because of you?
You are the one that got dumped my a man because you cannot control him.
Is it my fault for being dumped? It's your fault.
You were so rude talking about poop and other stuff at the meeting.
In the end you are on Jung Hoon's mother's side.
I can't believe i apologized to her for you, even if it hurt my pride.
- You sure would have begged.
- I ought to!
You are going to use violence since words don't work!
If you think that i'm a bad mother, then get out of this house.
Actually i was thinking that.
You think i can't do it?
Where are you going?
What's wrong with her?
She is acting like that because I went to meet Jung Hoon's mother.
Did something bad happen when you met her?
She isn't a normal woman.
I tried my best, but Hye Yoon is mad at me, because i met her.
Therefore you must change your image towards your daughters.
I don't need them. They have no idea how much i've done for them.
The one thinks that i'm cold hearted, without blood running to my vains.
And the other one doesn't even come to see me.
Hae Jin doesn't even answer your calls, after the meeting.
I think, this is not good at all.
I don't care if they don't answer my calls. Let's see if they can live happily.
Mom.
I knew you would do this. Why don't you answer my calls when you are home?
Why couldn't I contact you since that day? Is your husband having an affair?
Ask one thing at a time. Should I get you something to drink?
- What do you have?
- There is plum tea. I can make it into ice tea.
What did your husband do?
Talk to me.
I have only two daughters and they make me worry a lot.
Hye Yoon doesn't make you worry. It's just me that is causing problems.
Who told you that you are causing problems?
Who is the one who takes on the role as big sister?
There is nothing serious between me and my husband.
- Give me your cell phone.
- Why?
I told you to give me it.
This bastard!
I knew he would do this. I wondered what it was when I saw your expression that day.
You were overwhelmed when you saw this.
You really are persistent!
They say son in laws are bastards.
Tell this bastard to come here right now!
- It's useless.
- Why is it useless?
You must take the control of his money and this apartment now.
- I don't need anything.
- Why do you not need it? Idiot!
I told you constantly that you have to prepare for things like this.
It's not the first time his doing that.
Where is the phone? I should call.
Don't do this.
I don't want to live.
I don't want...
Don't delete the photo that the girl sent you.
I think it's too natural. I think more should have been inserted.
I think it will come out quickly.
I put it just fine, so it will not come out easily.
They do tell me I became pretty.
It will looks better the next week.
Thank you, director. You really do have god's hands.
What brings you here?
I warned you before that if you hurt my child, I won't stay still!
What's wrong?
Get back to work. Tell the patients to come back later and give them coupons.
Alright.
If you are done breaking things, lets have a convertation.
Conversation? That sounds good. Sit.
What are you going to do?
She wants divorce.
So you are going to divorce her? I knew you would do this.
People who abandoned their family once, they can do it again.
Is divorce that easy to you?
I need to get divorce with her, so i don't have to see you again.
How much are you going to give her, for compensation?
I will talk about it with my wife.
When you lived with her, you didn't treat her like a human.
Now that you getting divorce,you treating her like a human?
Do you have anything more to say?
I don't have anything to say right now. I think I will have things to say in the future about how you act.
I'm not going to be able to see dad before going to sleep again.
You must like dad a lot even though he scolds you.
When I am being scolded, I don't like it and then I forget about it quickly.
You are like that too, right? You get scolded by dad a lot.
Don't speak from now on. Since you are talking, you can't sleep when you have to.
Close your eyes.
Why are you being like this?
Hey, do you think you were the only one suffering? Do you know how much stress I went through?
Do you think a man has an affair for no reason? It's because he isn't satisfied when he is home.
I was ready to let it go, but now i can't because of your cheap mother.
Do you have the right to talk bad about my mom?
What my mom done wrong?
She did what supposed to do as my mom!
Is that wrong?
Actually i wasn't going to get a divorce.
But after i saw what she did to my hospital, i think i should get divorce.
If you want to become happy, you need to throw away your mom.
Right, you are her daughter.
I get it now.
I will give you 100.000.000 won for compensation, but i will take care my son.
How are you going to raise him?
I can't let your girlfriend take care of him.
Don't worry. I will hire a care mother for him.
Let's hurry and finished this. I don't want for us to get worse.
Your mind is collapsing. Yes, it would be weird if your mind wasn't collapsing.
Do you think he really did love me?
You have reached the state of denying the past.
Our love has now become the past.
- Do you want me to call Jung Hoon for you?
- You want to die?
Sang Jin oppa was concerned about you after you left like that.
I'm not interested.
He said he broke off the engagement.
During the preparation for the marriage, he said there were a lot of problems with the woman.
I think there are a lot of couples that break up while preparing for the marriage. Same goes for you two.
Hey, what did I do?
I'm just talking about what happens nowadays.
Instead of divorcing after the marriage, it's better to break it off while preparing for the marriage.
So our break up became a statistic now.
I wasn't talking about you two.
I was talking about other couples.
I'm going to go home. It doesn't feel comfortable here either.
Hey, don't be like this.
No, I am going to forget that narrow minded fool and live my life happily.
Bastard, how could he not call me even once?
Hey, it's only been a week since you guys broke up.
It's only been a week?
It's only been a week, but it feels like ten years that I suffered because of you.
It has been only one week since we broke up.
It feels like it's been a thousand years even though it's only been a week.
No way... I can't endure it for 1000 ye...
There was an accident. Wooil Hospital. Emergency room.
Do you know where the car accident patients are?
There are several car accident patients. What is there their name?
What happened? You said you got into an accident. I couldn't find your name.
It's because I came out without much measures.
Are you hurt anywhere? Car accidents have an aftereffect. Just because it doesn't hurt now doesn't mean you should leave.
Did you get hurt there?
No. The heart inside.
It was your heart? Not your body?
I was scared! How could you joke around like this?
I crossed when it was the red light.
I think there is something wrong with my mind.
It's only been a week since we broke up.
It feels like it's been a thousand years. How could it have only been a week?
- You don't love me.
- You are the one that doesn't love me.
How do you only receive and not give?
I grew up in a poor family, with the absence of my father.
I can get away from being poor with my own strength.
But, I can't get away from the fact I don't have a dad.
I was constantly looking for a father like man.
To me, you are a father like person.
I realize now that a father doesn't indulge everything.
I'll do well.
Do you know how scared I was? On my way here, I prayed to god again and again
for nothing bad to have happened to you.
I like you better than my mom. I can depend on you.
I'm scared that I was going to be thrown away because I like you too much.
I keep testing your love.
Who says that women have a higher level of maturity than men?
You are such a child.
Let's get married quickly.
Demand suit for divorce.
- I love you.
- Me too.
Don't say 'me too' and say 'I love you'.
I love you.
If you want to stop, say it now.
From now on, trust me and follow me.
What if you get tired like this time?
I said you must!
I'll trust you.
They must be in a hurry.
Look at this.
How did these people know we were getting married?
They know because I signed up to be a member. We need to move fast if we are going to get married.
What are you going to say to your parents?
I told you to trust me.
It's embarrassing.
I'll promise that something like this will never happen again.
Then let's go for our wedding!
Let's go!
- Where could it possibly be?
- What are you looking for?
Where is a dried squid?
You should put things like this where it can be easily found.
Think about what you did by yourself in the house.
Sit down.
I didn't stamp it. There was something we would have to agree upon before stamping.
What is it?
First, compensation. Second, division
of property. Third, custody.
I will take 100,000,000
won for compensation.
- Because you cheated on me.
- What the heck?
Are you saying you're
taking that money for me?
Give this house to me. Take your hospital.
But give me half of the land and five
studio and resorts you bought in cash.
Give me 500 won for custody.
We both have parental right.
This is what I ask.
- This is highway robbery.
- I've lived with you for seven years.
I have a right to be like this.
The actual maximum compensation
you can get is 5,000 won.
By law, you can't have that amount of money.
I'm being considerate now.
Just take that.
After you married me, your property
was increased by 300 percent.
I contributed to that.
Even by law, I have a chance of winning.
Maybe this is why people who are similar get married.
Young Mi wasn't like this.
You don't need to talk about your former wife.
I know you have a secret
fund but I won't touch that.
If I have to give you that
much, I won't divorce.
What?
I'm not going to do it because I don't want to give you money.
If you want to divorce me, lower the price.
When we got married, you treated me cheaply. When we are divorcing, you are still treating me cheaply.
I'm not letting this go.
We shouldn't have married in the beginning.
Because we didn't have trust that is the foundation of marriage.
You took that pill this morning.
Are you taking that again?
I need to take it so I
can calm my anger down.
You take vitamins often. You're going to
live until you put your shit on the wall.
I'm going to live healthy while I can.
You can take some too.
No. I don't want to.
I don't want to live longer.
Did something happen to Hae Jin? You
went to check on her a while ago.
I don't even want to talk about it.
Red at morning. Dead at eve. Little goods,
little care.
A son in law is a son of a bitch.
You're so funny, sis'.
I feel bad for him.
What's up? You went out as if you wouldn't come back.
We decided to get married.
Now you stay out of this. Jung Hoon
and I are going to take care of it.
If you can do it, then do it.
I'll stay out of it.
Why is mom like that?
You guys got back together because
she apologized to Jung Hoon's mom.
Did she?
I don't believe it.
She loves you guys in her own way.
There are some side effects, but you must not doubt her love for you two.
Why did she apologize? What did I
do wrong? What did we do wrong?
Mom.
- Did your husband come home?
- Yes.
What did he decide to do?
He says he can't divorce me because he doesn't want to give me money.
That bastard!
What a bad bastard!
What did you tell him? What are you going to do?
I don't know.
Did he say he will end it with the woman?
It doesn't matter if he has a woman or not. She won't be the first.
Can you stay in my house tomorrow?
He will leave sooner if you stay here.
Alright, let's settle this.
Do any of you care about one's career when your kid gets married?
Specifications are society's standards and can't be god's standards.
Love is not calculated.
If there are calculations in love, that means the nature of love has been lost.
The one thing that needs to come first in marriage is love.
Everyone, especially those who have children
we shouldn't make a marriage become a display that you can show off to others.
- Go home safely.
- Yes.
You worked hard.
Stella sister and Peter brother.
It has been long time since you all came to evening mass.
I know. Peter is getting married soon.
Congratulations.
Your service tonight was so good.
The sermon was just right for us.
Where are you having the marriage?
I wish I can do it in church.
Her parents-in-law want to have the wedding in a hotel.
I don't want to do it. But if they want it, I guess I have to follow them.
That's good!
Hae Yoon is so lucky.
I'm so jealous.
Your first son-in-law is the most successful plastic surgeon in Gang Nam.
And your second son in law is from a rich family.
It's not good for me.
It's good for them.
After Hae Yoon gets married,
shut down the store and stay home.
You can ask for your living expenses from your kids.
What are you talking about? I don't want to
be a burden to them. I can live by myself.
- Hey, Hae Yoon.
- Hi.
We were talking about you. I heard you are getting married at a five star hotel.
Even though you look pretty now, you must look more pretty when you get married in a hotel.
- Aren't you going to go business?
- I am going to.
I'm going to take this.
I'll pay you later.
Don't buy food and eat this.
- Where are you going?
- I'm meeting my mother in law.
Now you're becoming her family.
I'm sorry.
Don't be discouraged or lose focus because of what happened.
I decided to apologize to her because
I know how much you love him.
Who is going to become discouraged?
What is this?
It's a gift for you. I was going to give it
to you at the meeting but I forgot about it.
You didn't have to do this.
It's so pretty!
It's a couple of t-shirts made out of eco-friendly material.
It'd be good if I wear this when I go on a trip.
You can wear this at home too.
Thank you, Hye Yoon. I like it.
I want to live like you and father in law.
You will be able to.
They say that after the rain, the earth hardens.
I think that you two's love for each other became harder after what happened.
Yes, mother.
Since the wedding is in
January, we have to hurry up.
I wanted to have it at the Catholic Church. That's okay with you, right?
Didn't you say last time that we should have it at the hotel?
I changed my mind. Having it in the hotel is too common.
I thought it would hold more meaning to have it in the Catholic Church that Jung Hoon grew up in.
When is your mom free? I'm afraid to call her because she might be busy.
It's alright. You can call her anytime.
The two of them suit well together.
Do you know that woman?
I saw her for the first time today.
Then how do you know her?
Ki Joong is marrying two weeks before you guys.
So she must be his fiance.
Aunt, you came? Hye Yoon, you are here too.
This is Han Chae Young.
Hello.
I thought I'm going to see you at dinner next week.
I think in my family, I am the first to see you.
- You are right, aunt.
- This is my future daughter in law.
Your bracelet looks pretty. It would look pretty on you too.
If you want it, I'll tell them to have one for you.
It's alright.
Not the same one. It's a little weird when you two aren't even sisters.
There isn't anything more pretty than this in this brand.
What is pretty is subjective. You can't rank beauty.
My aunt is that romantic.
I think it won't fit with Hye Yoon. Aren't you practical person?
It's because you don't know me well. I am romantic too.
Yes, you are saying that because you don't know Hye Yoon well.
Look at this. She bought me a couple t-shirts.
It's pretty, right?
I can't argue about that. It'd look good on you.
You think so too, right? It's also made of eco-friendly material.
You look so excited. You always wanted to
have a daughter. Your dream came true.
Yeah. We're going to write a new history
of mother-in-law and daughter-in-law.
I thought you're not going to spend
any money on Hae Yoon's wedding.
She's having a wedding at a hotel.
I should at least spend money on something.
I can't just sit there and do nothing.
You can't borrow money from the bank?
They said I can't do it anymore. By the
way, why don't you have any money?
Didn't you save some money?
- I did.
- Then let me borrow it. I'll pay you back.
It'd be better to use your money.
I don't want to pay for the interest.
But I lent it to somebody.
No way. Why did you do that?
You shouldn't have done it.
I had to do it.
She needed money urgently.
- Is she going to pay you back?
- Of course.
Should I borrow 20,000,000 won?
Just borrow 10,000,000 won for now.
Yeah. You're doing the right thing.
Hae Jin didn't have a proper wedding.
Hae Yoon is the first one who can have a good wedding in our family.
Don't ever say that in front of Hae Jin.
Why not?
She's happy now.
Ki Joong's fiance is the youngest daughter of Jae Il group's CEO.
I think she's kind of spoiled.
Why do you think that?
Just like she's in the center of this world,
she thinks what she wears is the prettiest.
I don't usually gossip about other people.
I'm telling you this because it's you.
I know, mother.
It's there.
- How does this look?
- It's okay.
I don't like that answer.
You should like it very much.
Yes.
Then what about this?
I'm really going to go crazy. What should I say to please her?
Mother, you choose it for me. Your style is classy and I like it.
Really? Alright, I'll choose it for you.
- Please show us this.
- Alright, madam.
I rode the taxi with Hye Yoon.
Hye Yoon, let's take a picture.
Look here.
One, two...
Let's take another picture with your bracelet in it.
- Yes.
- So it shows well.
Hye Yoon, look here.
They're looking good.
Shoot.
But I should save my fiance's face.
Don't make that look.
- I don't like that.
- We're over.
You can't just cut off our relationship
like you cut off a fruit or something.
You should know because you're old enough.
This will only hurt you.
I am not marrying you. I won't touch your wife. In that case, we can still meet, right?
Even if we break up, I'm not going to keep the studio.
If I wanted your money, I wouldn't have come here.
- Please wait a moment.
- Alright, I understand.
Even a woman like her has plastic surgery.
I think she does everything.
Hey, have a seat here.
What's up?
This is the money you paid for the meal at the meeting.
Why would you bring me this? I paid because I felt bad for being late.
You can buy me dinner or something later.
A man doesn't have to pay for this. A woman
can pay for this too. Or they do dutch.
It doesn't really matter.
I wanted to make points from Hae Yoon's mother but I missed it.
Mother in law?
It's a good time.
Since we are a family, let's become closer. Invite me to your house as well.
Alright.
I'll go now. The lunch period for my company is going to end.
Think carefully about marriage.
I'm saying you still have a chance to run away before you walk into the the wedding hall.
I want to go into the wedding hall quickly.
Since it has been decided, I want to get it over with.
Maybe you need some rest. Do you want to go home?
No, mother.
You shouldn't feel tired at your age just because of this.
Yes.
I told you to come because I had something to tell you.
To be married in a Catholic Church, you have to be qualified.
What qualification?
You need to learn some stuff about church and you also need to go see the priest.
At this opportunity, I would like to tell you to decide on a religion, but since religion is your choice, you decide.
It's from smoke into smother...
Are you going on a trip?
No, I'm going to Hae Jin's house.
How long are you going to stay?
This should bring at least those to sleep over at her house.
What is that?
Mother bought it for me.
She should give you something bigger instead of spending money on unnecessary things.
- How much is it?
- If you hear it, you will faint.
Let's hear it so I can faint. How much is it?
3,000,000 won.
She must be crazy. I had to loan money because I don't have enough money for the wedding.
Did you really do that?
She wants to have your wedding at the hotel. I should at least do that.
She says she wants to have it in a Catholic Church instead of a hotel.
What nonsense is that?
She was the one who wanted to have the wedding at the hotel!
You didn't like that idea though.
Because it costs so much.
Come to think of it, I think they're going pay
for the place since they want to do it there.
It wasn't something I should object.
You only get married once in your life time. It looks good when others see it.
So what did you say to her?
I stayed silent.
What did Jung Hoon say?
I didn't hear anything from Jung Hoon. He probably will follow his mother's words.
Hey! What are you going to after getting married if you can't even control your man?
If you're going to live like this, call off the engagement!
Mom!
I don't want you to feel small. You know how Hae Jin lives with Do Hyun.
Think straight! Once you get controlled by him, then you're going to keep losing.
- Why did you call me here?
- You surprised me.
If somebody saw, they would think we are getting married here.
We can tell them we are getting married here.
It really feels like we are getting married once you step up here.
Do you remember when I said if I could do whatever I wanted and you said I could?
Yes.
But I can't really do what I want.
And the wedding hall too. Why didn't you tell me the location was changed to the Catholic Church?
It hasn't been decided yet. We have to hear your mother's opinion too.
If mother wants to have it there, we have to do that.
- Does what my mom says have an effect?
- Of course.
If I think about how you dumped me because of your mom, I get so upset.
Since that, my opinion is ignored.
You said we won't speak of that again.
It became a trauma.
I think from now on whenever anything happens, I will mention it again.
You said you would trust me and follow me. This is not trusting me.
I keep being like this unconsciously. You need to show me more affection than last time for it to end.
I'll be the first and the last person who has the wedding in my family.
My mom wants it to be the most meaningful.
I grew up there and it affected my life.
It might be a place full of memories for you, but it's a strange place for me.
Also, I heard that you have to get an education to get married there. That is too much for me.
Then what do you want to do?
It's not that I don't want to get married at the Catholic Church, but I want to do it here.
I also have romance for my wedding.
I want to shine that day.
Alright, I'll take care of it.
You're going to listen to your mom anyway!
Hye Yoon.
Don't look! Don't look until I get up.
Alright, I turned around.
I turned around.
Did you get up yet? I'm turning around.
I'm turning.
Ahjussi, please go.
Hye Yoon!
You know how there is depression for when you are living? Is there one for marriage as well?
I don't know why we can't negotiate at least one thing.
Why does 'I'll take care of it' sound so empty?
Why is where you get married important? It's the person you are getting married to that is important.
You will know if you start preparing for the wedding.
I can't believe it. I was trying to polish the apple for Jung Hoon's mom all day.
But you got a expensive bracelet. You got a brand name bag last time too.
I'd polish the apple 100 times if I can get those.
Think about living like that forever. Is that really good?
What are you doing? Others might think you have a fetish.
What's that?
I know you know what it means. You don't have to act innocent.
Oh my gosh.
If it isn't because of this, I wouldn't have to meet a person like you.
- Let's go, bro.
- Do you also not know what an orgasm is?
Do you want to die?
Who is the new comer?
Who is it that we have to come here?
Aunt?
Long time no see, Do Hyun.
We can drink a beer.
No. You shouldn't drive after you drink.
She follows rules very well.
You aren't going to come continuously, right?
How could you ask him why he brought me here in front of me?
I came here because he told me I should go with him. He told me he would introduce me to good men.
I want you to like me.
Even if you are my hyung, I can't see you acting like that.
You thought well. Go home early.
My sister said that she would sleep at your house as well.
Mother in law is sleeping in my house?
She says she will sleep there because Hye Jin is not in a good condition.
Hello.
This is Jung Hoon's mother. Can we talk on the phone?
If you are running your store...
It's alright. What could be more important than business concerning my child.
Do you have some time tomorrow? I think we need to talk about our children's marriage.
How about you come to Gang Buk this time?
As you know, I am a working person so it is not easy to find time in the morning.
I understand. I will go there.
Yes. Yes.
How could she phrase it like that? Is it easy for me to find time in the morning?
Hey, you're back.
Did you eat?
Mom, can't we just have the marriage at the hotel?
Did Hye Yoon say something?
No. Actually, Hae Yoon doesn't have much free time.
And it's hard for her to do it at church. We only thought about ourselves.
Hye Yoon is very weird. She should have said something a while ago.
I told you that Hye Yoon didn't say anything.
Idiot! Since you are being like this, it makes it seem more likely that Hye Yoon said something.
If you wanted to take her side, you should've done it better.
These two women are making me crazy.
Shoot.
Give me a glass too.
I'm trying to get along with Hae Yoon but if he acts like that, I really don't want to try.
Did he say something?
He is jumpy. It looks like Hye Yoon said something to him about the wedding hall.
It is your assumption that Hye Yoon said something.
My assumption is right. If it is not, he wouldn't be acting like this when he was alright with it yesterday.
If that's what they want, then let them do it at a hotel.
We told the priest that we want to have the wedding at the church.
You said that unpredictably.
I looked into and there are no spaces at the hotel and they have been fully booked.
Also, because of the fact that January 5th is a lucky day, there are no spaces left.
So I thought they were meant to have their wedding at church.
Then we can't do anything.
Yes. I told the Catholic Church executive office that Jung Hoon is getting married on that day.
We can't cancel it.
Already?
I'm the person to execute the plan after deciding.
Then what should we do?
I need to meet with Hye Yoon's mother and talk with her.
She didn't like to have the wedding at a hotel so she will agree with me.
- You came quickly.
- I came quickly because my child needs me.
I'm sorry for making you worry when you must be busy with Hye Yoon's wedding.
Don't think of it as making me worry. It's good that you aren't suffering by yourself and looking for me.
Let's have something delicious to eat.
Let's just order it. I know you're not in a mood for that.
This is why that bastard thinks you are easy to deal with.
I knew you would come.
Why is mother in law at home? I'll go in when she leaves.
Just like you told me, I need a man to make a move.
Where's a blanket?
Sleep in here.
What will you do when your husband comes home?
He isn't coming home. So, let's sleep in here together.
- Why isn't he coming home?
- He found out you came.
He is avoiding me?
Don't bother him at his hospital. It doesn't do any good when we divorce.
- Where did he say he will sleep?
- He will probably sleep in the hospital.
Is it certain? He is with that woman, right?
That woman is not what is important.
Why isn't she important when she is the mail culprit of destroying the family?
You can also ask her for compensation.
I don't want to do that.
- You still have some left.
- What?
You still have some feelings left for your husband.
- You can't divorce with those feelings.
- It's not that.
Even if you get a divorce, there will be men like him around you.
In addition, you have a child.
Think about it well. You can break it off anytime.
But you have to break it off when you want to. Don't do it because your husband tells you to.
From what I can see, you aren't certain yet.
You have to be more careful about divorce than marriage.
Do you think it's easy for a single woman to live while raising a child?
Look at your mother. It is hard.
You weren't happy when dad was alive.
How can you tell just by looking at the outside of a couple's relationship?
We had a deep relationship though. He didn't make a lot of money.
Everything else about him was good.
I think of him a lot when I prepared for your wedding.
Do you know how it feels to prepare a kid's wedding alone?
Thank you for coming all the way over here.
It's not a big deal. We've always met at Gangnam.
Of course I should come here this time.
- You look annoyed.
- Me?
No, I don't.
Didn't you want to have the wedding at church because of family reasons?
No, it's not. Our family is still good.
I'm glad to hear that. I was kind of worried.
The reason why I choose church was that it's very meaningful, not because of money.
I see. Now I don't need to worry.
I guess Hae Yoon doesn't like to have her wedding at church.
It's not that.
I think people around her told her...
a woman like you deserves to have a wedding at a hotel.
If you were a woman, wouldn't you like to have your wedding at a hotel?
I didn't know she is easily influenced by others.
You said you want to do it at the hotel at the meeting.
So we decided to do it at a hotel just like you said.
Really?
I don't know if you know how it feels.
Disappointed when I was prepared to eat
beef but a chef gives me pasta instead.
- Please give me a glass of water.
- Okay.
Did Hae Yoon come here yet?
She didn't because I don't see her.
Why is she not here yet?
Hey, this is a new toy that my company made.
I can put this right next to the other one.
- You met my mom, didn't you?
- Yeah.
Can't your family afford to have a wedding at a hotel?
I don't think so.
I think she's very confused. You need to help her at this kind of situation.
Hae Yoon decided to marry you because she trusts you.
I know.
Did you forget what you did to Hae Yoon
last time? Are you going to do that again?
Why aren't you answering?
No. I will do everything.
Good. A woman's behavior depends on her man.
If you're good to her, she will do better.
- Hi. Take this.
- You didn't have to do this.
Unless it's really delicious, I don't eat cake.
It makes me fat.
- Okay.
- Come here. I need to talk to you.
Sure.
I think I have to say words unpleasant to the ear.
Who I hate the most is a person who's not honest.
I tried to get along with you
but you stabbed me in the back.
It's a misunderstanding.
Why didn't you tell me that you don't
want to have the wedding at church?
If you had told me that, I would've found another way.
It's not that I don't like church.
Don't act nice and innocent in front of me.
It doesn't last long just like this time.
I'm sorry.
- Where's Mom?
- Hae Yoon is here.
Are you getting mad because of what I said?
Can I not say this?
Of course you can.
Do you know what I heard from your mother?
She asked me if I have family reasons.
It means we look poor.
I can endure anything but not this one.
You have the heir of the rich.
Thank you. It's very comforting to me.
You came?
Why are you yelling at her?
What did she do wrong?
I wasn't yelling. I was just telling her what I have to.
If Hae Yoon had told me her opinion,
this wouldn't have happened.
I was humiliated by her mother.
You are the one who changed your mind!
If you didn't change your mind,
none of this would've happened!
Hae Jung Hoon!
She's my girl! I can't see her
getting insulted by anybody!
I was just talking to her!
Ask her if I insulted her!
- Hae Yoon...
- No, you didn't.
You should've told me if you come to my house.
Why are you getting insulted?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
You said it traumatized you.
You told me to show you how much I love you.
So I did. I got you out of there in front of
my mother even if it was very rude!
I did what you wanted me to.
What's wrong now?
Why can't you find
a good time to do that?
Don't do that. It hurts.
Of course it hurts you. You need more.
Why did you tell her like that?
That's what you want.
Do you know how hard I tried to get along with her?
I even became her avatar!
What about me then? I paid 5,000,000 won to Do Hyun to save your face.
And I went to see your mom whenever she wants to see me.
I tried my best but all she said was be good to you.
You have a real lack of courtesy toward adults.
What?
They can say words that you don't want to hear.
You can't even stand that you have to make things worse?
You think we can do this marriage?
We decided not to say controversial words to each other.
Even if we get married, we won't be happy
because we lost favor in her eyes!
- Stop!
- If I don't, are you going to dump me again?
Then do it.
If I had known that my mom apologized to your
mom earlier, I wouldn't have clung to you.
What did my mom do so wrong that
she had to apologize to your mom?
Can't she even show off her daughter?
Talk about the present. If we start talking
about past, it will make things worse.
Fine. For us, past is something
that will make us worse.
How am I supposed to see your mother again?
Dad.
What are you doing there?
You should follow her.
Are you not going home?
There's nobody that welcomes me at home.
I'm just going to do this.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Where's Hae Yoon?
Would you like to drink with me?
I'm in.
You ignored my calls so I had to come here.
But it's too late now.
I don't want an awkward relationship with you.
Why did you ignore my calls? I thought
you were still mad or something.
I thought you'd live a happy life with a
daughter of a famous law firm company.
I thought I could use her for my ambition.
But I was eventually controlled by her.
You are a lawyer. You will meet a great woman.
After I got hurt, I realized that having
a comfortable relationship is the best.
I missed you.
Go home and don't ever make that look.
Don't come find me.
Answer the phone. I don't have to come here then.
- Who is he?
- Mom.
- Hi.
- I haven't seen him before.
- We went to college together. Go now.
- I'm going to go even if you tell me not to.
I will see you later.
- Who is he?
- Where were you?
- I was with Hae Jin.
- You go there often.
Do Hyun would hate it.
I don't care if he does or not.
- What does he do?
- He's a lawyer.
A lawyer? Is he married?
Of course, he is.
What was a married man doing here?
I met Jung Hoon's mom and she
said she will think about it.
I know.
How do you know?
I'm not going to share any information with you.
Why aren't you answering?
A life is lonely. It's something I have to go through.
- You were from her house, weren't you?
- How did you know?
I knew it. What did she say?
It's my fault. When she asked
me about church, I said okay.
She told me if I told her what I really think about it, she would've found another way.
It's not easy to say what you really
think in front of a mother-in-law.
Maybe that's what she did to her mother-in-law.
What did Jung Hoon say?
What Jung Hoon thinks is the most important.
No parents can win their kids.
Mom, please don't call Jung Hoon.
If she calls me to meet her, I
feel awkward and uncomfortable.
He will feel the same.
That's a marriage. He has to get used to it.
So do you.
Be careful.
Put him in.
I thought he didn't drink that much but he's so drunk.
It happens sometimes. I'll see you later.
Okay.
Bye.
I'm alone. No. I have Do Hyun.
I'm so lonely. I'm happy if somebody bothers me.
I wish someone could stay with me.
Mom, I can eat by myself.
Really?
I want to show Dad that I can eat by myself
after he gets back from the business trip.
Okay.
Have you rode a motorcycle with him?
My husband's girlfriend is in the friend list.
What a good world.
Mom, can you come watch my kid now?